<resources>

    <string name="app_name">My Optimize</string>
    <string name="care">Attentions</string>
    <string name="problem">Problems</string>
    <string name="exit_warning">Press again to exit</string>
    <string name="giving_up_modifies">Press again to give up and step back</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="care_type">Type：</string>
    <string name="create">Create</string>
    <string name="color">Color：</string>
    <string name="empty_title_warning">Title can\'t be empty !</string>
    <string name="confirm">Yes</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="archive">Archive</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="create_new_care_item">Add new attention</string>
    <string name="sort">Sort</string>
    <string name="tips">Tips</string>
    <string name="options">Options</string>
    <string name="edit_description">Edit description</string>
    <string name="save_changes">save changes</string>
    <string name="care_item_details">Attention details</string>
    <string name="delete">delete</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="properties">Properties</string>
    <string name="created_at">Created at：</string>
    <string name="existed_time">Existed for：</string>
    <string name="achieved">ACHIEVED</string>
    <string name="unachieved">UNACHIEVED</string>
    <string name="days">Days</string>
    <string name="delete_warning">Are you sure you want to delete it?</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="edit_description_title">Edit description title</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="do_archive">Archive</string>
    <string name="archive_confirm">Are you sure you want to archive it?</string>
    <string name="archive_warning">The attention item hasn\'t been achieved yet, are you sure you want to give up and archive it?</string>
    <string name="give_up_confirm">Are you really sure you want to give up?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="unarchive_warning">Are you sure you want to unarchive?</string>
    <string name="unarchive_tip">Welcome back! And please don\'t give up this time~</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="lasted_time">Lasted time：</string>
    <string name="achieved_at">Achieved at：</string>
    <string name="archived_at">Archived at：</string>
    <string name="goal">Goal：</string>
    <string name="punishment">Punishment：</string>
    <string name="progress">Progress</string>
    <string name="records">Records</string>
    <string name="progress_bar_title">Progress</string>
    <string name="succeeded">succeeded：</string>
    <string name="failed">failed：</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="succeeded_">Succeeded</string>
    <string name="failed_">Failed</string>
    <string name="confirm_">Confirm</string>
    <string name="today_is">Today is：</string>
    <string name="progress_">Progress：</string>
    <string name="succeeded__">Succeeded：</string>
    <string name="failed__">Failed：</string>
    <string name="percentage">Percentage：</string>
    <string name="calendar_view">Calendar</string>
    <string name="no_record_selected">You haven\'t selected any record</string>
    <string name="modified">Modified：</string>
    <string name="care_has_not_been_created">The attention Item hasn\'t been created at this time</string>
    <string name="day_has_not_come_yet">That day has not come yet</string>
    <string name="care_item_has_been_archived">The attention Item has been archived at this time</string>
    <string name="period_length">Period：</string>
    <string name="every">Every</string>
    <string name="signed_in">Signed in</string>
    <string name="signed_out">Signed out</string>
    <string name="sub_goal">Sub-Goal：</string>
    <string name="sub_progress_zero">Sub-progress is 0</string>
    <string name="sub_progress">Sub：</string>
    <string name="sign_time_limitation">Sign-time limitation：</string>
    <string name="end_time_less_than_start_time"><![CDATA[End time <= start time]]></string>
    <string name="current_time_out_of_limitation">The current time is out of sign-time limitation</string>
    <string name="everyday">Everyday</string>
    <string name="sign_time_limitation_">Sign-time limitation</string>
    <string name="care_item_auto_sort">Sort attention items by status</string>
    <string name="backup">Backup</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="chinese_simplified">简体中文</string>
    <string name="english_us">English (United States)</string>
    <string name="backup_confirm">Please enter the backup file\'s name</string>
    <string name="backed_up_at">Backed up at</string>
    <string name="recover">Recover</string>
    <string name="create_new_problem_item">Add new problem</string>
    <string name="rank">Rank：</string>
    <string name="problem_item_auto_sort">Sort problem item by rank</string>
    <string name="archive_warning_problem">The problem hasn\'t been solved yet, are you sure you want to give up and archive it?</string>
    <string name="analysis">Analysis</string>
    <string name="solution">Solution</string>
    <string name="status">Status：</string>
    <string name="solved">Solved</string>
    <string name="solving">Solving</string>
    <string name="solved_at">Solved at：</string>
    <string name="app_version">Version：1.0.0</string>
    <string name="introduction">Introduction</string>
    <string name="developer">Developer</string>
    <string name="links">Links</string>
    <string name="contact_developer">Contact developer</string>
    <string name="help_translate">Help with translation</string>
    <string name="view_source_code">View source code on Github</string>
    <string name="support_developer">Support the developer</string>
    <string name="rate_app">Rate this app</string>
    <string name="app_introduction"><![CDATA[\t\tMy Optimize is an app used for helping people optimize themselves.Its main function is to help people achieve the things that they want to persist & help people solve problems. For more information, please refer to：navigation drawer menu -> help]]></string>
    <string name="share_text"><![CDATA[My Optimize is an app used for helping people optimize themselves.Its main function is to help people achieve the things that they want to persist & help people solve problems. Welcome to use：https://github.com/OneCivilization/MyWorld/raw/master/MyOptimize/MyOptimize-release.apk]]></string>
    <string name="email_not_supported">Your phone hasn\'t installed any Email-sending app, please send Email to onecivilization.cn@gmail.com manually</string>
    <string name="alipay">Alipay：</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="rate_not_supported">Can\'t find any App Market application</string>
    <string name="user_guide">User Guide</string>
    <string name="paypal">PayPal：</string>
    <string name="alipay_account">2391682070@qq.com</string>
    <string name="paypal_account">onecivilization.cn@gmail.com</string>

    <string name="help_introduction"><![CDATA[\t\tMy Optimize is an application used for helping people improve themselves. The application has two main functions: 1.Help people achieve what they want to persist. 2. Help people solve problems in their daily life.\n\n\t\tBefore introducing the first function, we would like to introduce a concept first: attentions. Attentions represent the things that we want to persist, it can be the habits we want to form (e.g. Keep early hours, Exercise three times a week), the new changes we want to make (e.g. Become more outgoing, Exercise more), and the reactions we want to take when meet specific events (e.g. Not to play mobile phones before sleeping, Not to smoke in public). Obviously it’s not appropriate to call all of them “habits”. Since they all need attention, here we call them “attentions”. In this app, you can help yourself achieve what you want to persist by creating “attentions”.\n\n\t\tIn this app you can create six kinds of Attentions: \n\n\t\t1. Plain Text\n\n\t\t\tYou can write some words on it to remind yourself the changes you want to make. For example: “Become more outgoing”, “Keep a good mood”. For each plain text attention, you can set its color to change its visual appearance.\n\n2. Event-driven\n\n\t\t\tYou can record your reaction to a specific event when it happens. For example: “Not to play mobile phone before sleeping”, “Not to smoke in public”. When creating an event-driven attention, you need to set its goal and punishment. It works like this: the goal is the total times that you want to react to the event positively, the punishment is the number that will be subtracted from the progress when you take a negative reaction, and the progress is calculated by the following formula: progress = your positive reaction times – your negative reaction times * punishment. When progress reaches your goal, this attention is achieved. You can modify the records in the calendar view, but in order to maintain the authenticity of records, your modification times will be shown at the upper right corner of the calendar.\n\n3. Periodic\n\n\t\t\tYou can record your habit forming process on it, and the habit need to be periodic. For example: “Keep early hours”, “Exercise three times a week”. When creating a periodic attention, besides the goal and punishment, you also need to set its periodic time (the minimum is 1 day). You can record and cancel the record repeatedly in a single cycle, but when the cycle is passed, you can’t modify the existing record. When the new cycle starts, the state of attention will refresh automatically.\n\n\t\t\tMoreover, you can attach two additional attribute with it: sub-item number and record time limitation. When you set sub-item number, then in a single cycle you can record as many times as the number you set, for example: “Exercise three times a week”, since in a single cycle you need to record 3 times, you should set its sub-item number to 3. When you set record time limitation, than only in the time you set can you do recording. The two attribute can also be combined together, for example: “Keep early hours”, you can set its sub-item number to 2 and record time limitation to “6:30-7:30, 21:30-22:30”.\n\n\t\tFor all kinds of attention, you can edit a text called “description” to record some information about this attention, like the attention’s creating background, the reason why you created it, its significance or something else. By the way, the text’s title is also editable, about the way to edit it please refer to the “tips” on “attentions details” interface.\n\n\t\tWe use color and the pattern on the check button to show the current status of an attention. When progress is minus，it is red & cross, but if the attention is checked, it is blue & tick; when 0<=progress<goal, if the attention is checked, it is blue & tick, else it is orange & the mark of attention’s type (plain text with no mark, event-driven with a circle, periodic with a horizontal line, periodic that has sub-items with the sub-progress number); when progress>=goal, it is green & tick. By the way, to check an attention item, you can either click the check button in the attentions list interface or click the progress bar in the attention details interface.\n\n\t\tThat is all about the app’s first function: Help people achieve what they want to persist. Now let’s see about its second function: Help people solve problems in their daily life. In our daily life, we usually feel unhappy, sad, or fidgety. Whatever it is, if we don’t feel happy, there must be something wrong in our life, which means we need to find the problem and try to solve it, or things would only become even worse. When you find the problem, no matter what the problem is, it can be solved through 3 steps: 1. Describe the problem: make clear about its background, result and seriousness, then define it in your own language; 2. Analyze the problem: find out what caused the problem, you may use the information in step 1 to help you work it out; 3. Solve the problem: give out you solution according to problem’s cause. Based on this simple but useful theory, you can help yourself solve your problems by creating “problem” in this app. A “problem” include 3 texts that can record your description, analyzation and solution of the problem. Maybe this theory seems too simple and useless, but if you practice it with rational thinking, you will find out that it’s invincible. In addition, you can think about how to solve the problem at any time, and write down you thinking result when you are convenient to open your phone. Moreover, generally don’t expect to solve the problem within only several days, because solving a problem is not such easy. Therefore, don’t give up solving a problem simply because you can’t solve it quickly, it’s ok to just write down the problem and solve it when you have time.\n\n\t\tThat’s all about this app’s main function, and now we need to make one thing clear: This app can’t optimize you, because the only thing it does is recording, it can only help you optimize yourself. Optimizing yourself is your job, and this app’s job is to record your stories when you are doing this job, just like a paper. Therefore, this app only fit for those who are optimizing themselves and is finding a tool to record their stories.\n\n\t\tNext let’s see about some miscellaneous functions. You can share your “attention” and “problem” to others as a long screenshot by clicking the share button on the top of the detail interface, and the picture will also be saved at SD-card/My Optimize/Screenshots. In settings, we offered 3 functions: set the way of sorting the attentions/problem; backup your data; set app’s language. About the first function, if you disable the auto-sorting option, then you can sort your attentions/problems by dragging them, but if the auto-sorting option is on, this is disabled. About the second function, the data is backed up at SD-card/My Optimize/Backup. About the third function, at present we only offered Simplified Chinese and English (US). The English is translated by the developer, so there might be some translation errors, if you find translation errors or is willing to help us translate the app to more languages, please click sliding menu -> feedback or sliding menu -> about -> help with translation.\n\n\t\tFinally, this app is developed by the OneCivilization team, and belongs to the “My World” App series (including logging, mind managing, planning and task managing and optimizing apps, at present only the last one is developed). In addition, this is an open source project and uses GPL3 license. You can view its source code by clicking sliding menu -> about -> view source code on github. If you think it’s a great app, welcome to click sliding menu -> share or sliding menu -> about -> rate this app/support the developer.\n\n\n * Here we only offer an overall introduction, for more details, please refer to tips (with a bulb icon) on the top of every interface.]]></string>
    <string name="tips_main_1"><![CDATA[* For overall introduction, please refer to sliding menu -> help.\n\n* You can check an attention by clicking the black checking button on the left of it.\n\n* The white number on the right of the attention represents the current progress of it.\n\n* We use color and the pattern on the check button to show the current status of an attention: When progress is minus，it is red & cross, but if the attention is checked, it is blue & tick; when 0<=progress<goal, if the attention is checked, it is blue & tick, else it is orange & the mark of attention’s type (plain text with no mark, event-driven with a circle, periodic with a horizontal line, periodic that has sub-items with the sub-progress number); when progress>=goal, it is green & tick.\n\n* We offered two ways to sort attentions: 1.Sort by attention’s status automatically; 2.Sort by dragging. You can set it at sliding menu -> settings, if you disable the auto-sorting option, then you can sort your attentions by dragging them, but if the auto-sorting option is on, this is disabled.]]></string>
    <string name="tips_main_2"><![CDATA[* For overall introduction, please refer to sliding menu -> help.\n\n* The white number on the right of the problem represents its lasting days.\n\n* We use color to show the rank of a problem: low – blue; normal – orange; high – red; extra high – purple.\n\n* We offered two ways to sort problems: 1.Sort by problem’s rank automatically; 2.Sort by dragging. You can set it at sliding menu -> settings, if you disable the auto-sorting option, then you can sort your problems by dragging them, but if the auto-sorting option is on, this is disabled.]]></string>
    <string name="tips_main_3" formatted="false"><![CDATA[* For overall introduction, please refer to sliding menu -> help.\n\n* Archived attentions are sorted by their archived time.\n\n* We use color and the pattern on the check button to show the completion level of an archived attention: <=0% – red & cross; 0%~60% – orange & horizontal line; 60%~100% – blue & horizontal line; >=100% – green & tick.]]></string>
    <string name="tips_main_4"><![CDATA[* For overall introduction, please refer to sliding menu -> help.\n\n* Archived problems are sorted by their archived time\n\n* The white number on the right of the problem represents the days between its created time and archived time.\n\n* If the problem is solved, its color is green, else it shows its rank’s color.]]></string>
    <string name="tips_new_care">* For periodic attention, if you want to start it at tomorrow but not today, you can check the option “Activate at tomorrow”.\n\n* Attentions represent the things that we want to persist, it can be the habits we want to form (e.g. Keep early hours, Exercise three times a week), the new changes we want to make (e.g. Become more outgoing, Exercise more), and the reactions we want to take when meet specific events (e.g. Not to play mobile phones before sleeping, Not to smoke in public). Obviously it’s not appropriate to call all of them “habits”. Since they all need attention, here we call them “attentions”. In this app, you can help yourself achieve what you want to persist by creating “attentions”.\n\n\t\tIn this app you can create six kinds of Attentions: \n\n\t\t1. Plain Text\n\n\t\t\tYou can write some words on it to remind yourself the changes you want to make. For example: “Become more outgoing”, “Keep a good mood”. For each plain text attention, you can set its color to change its visual appearance.\n\n\t\t2. Event-driven\n\n\t\t\tYou can record your reaction to a specific event when it happens. For example: “Not to play mobile phone before sleeping”, “Not to smoke in public”. When creating an event-driven attention, you need to set its goal and punishment. It works like this: the goal is the total times that you want to react to the event positively, the punishment is the number that will be subtracted from the progress when you take a negative reaction, and the progress is calculated by the following formula: progress = your positive reaction times – your negative reaction times * punishment. When progress reaches your goal, this attention is achieved. You can modify the records in the calendar view, but in order to maintain the authenticity of records, your modification times will be shown at the upper right corner of the calendar.\n\n\t\t3. Periodic\n\n\t\t\tYou can record your habit forming process on it, and the habit need to be periodic. For example: “Keep early hours”, “Exercise three times a week”. When creating a periodic attention, besides the goal and punishment, you also need to set its periodic time (the minimum is 1 day). You can record and cancel the record repeatedly in a single cycle, but when the cycle is passed, you can’t modify the existing record. When the new cycle starts, the state of attention will refresh automatically.\n\n\t\t\tMoreover, you can attach two additional attribute with it: sub-item number and record time limitation. When you set sub-item number, then in a single cycle you can record as many times as the number you set, for example: “Exercise three times a week”, since in a single cycle you need to record 3 times, you should set its sub-item number to 3. When you set record time limitation, than only in the time you set can you do recording. The two attribute can also be combined together, for example: “Keep early hours”, you can set its sub-item number to 2 and record time limitation to “6:30-7:30, 21:30-22:30”.\n\n\t\tFor all kinds of attention, you can edit a text called “description” to record some information about this attention, like the attention’s creating background, the reason why you created it, its significance or something else. By the way, the text’s title is also editable, about the way to edit it please refer to the “tips” on “attentions details” interface.</string>
    <string name="tips_description">* “Description” is an editable text that can be used for recording attention’s background, creating reason, persisting motivation, stories or something else you’d like to write down. By the way, this text’s title is also editable, you can edit it by clicking its title. </string>
    <string name="tips_text_care">* You can edit the title by clicking it, but the title can’t be empty.\n\n* “Description” is an editable text that can be used for recording attention’s background, creating reason, persisting motivation, stories or something else you’d like to write down. By the way, this text’s title is also editable, you can edit it by clicking the last edited time text at the bottom of description.\n\n* In “properties” interface, you can change attention’s status by clicking the status button.\n\n* In “properties” interface, you can change attention’s color, but if the attention is achieved, its color will be locked to be green.\n\n* You can share your attention to your friends as a long screenshot by clicking the share button on the title bar, the screenshot will be saved at SD-card/My Optimize/Screenshots.\n\n* Plain Text Attention: \n\n\t\tYou can write some words on it to remind yourself the changes you want to make. For example: “Become more outgoing”, “Keep a good mood”. For each plain text attention, you can set its color to change its visual appearance.</string>
    <string name="tips_nonperiodic_care">* You can edit the title by clicking it, but the title can’t be empty.\n\n* “Description” is an editable text that can be used for recording attention’s background, creating reason, persisting motivation, stories or something else you’d like to write down. By the way, this text’s title is also editable, you can edit it by clicking the last edited time text at the bottom of description.\n\n* In “progress” interface, you can add a record by clicking the progress bar.\n\n* In “records” interface, you can view/edit your records by clicking the dates on the calendar. Moreover, we use color to show the status of a day, blue represents it’s this attention’s creating day, green represents there is positive record at this day, red represents there is negative record at this day, gray represents there is records at this day, but the day’s progress is 0, today is highlighted as deep blue. \n\n* If you have modified the records, your modification times will be shown at the upper right corner of the calendar.\n\n* You can share your attention to your friends as a long screenshot by clicking the share button on the title bar, the screenshot will be saved at SD-card/My Optimize/Screenshots.\n\n* Event-driven Attention: \n\n\t\tYou can record your reaction to a specific event when it happens. For example: “Not to play mobile phone before sleeping”, “Not to smoke in public”. When creating an event-driven attention, you need to set its goal and punishment. It works like this: the goal is the total times that you want to react to the event positively, the punishment is the number that will be subtracted from the progress when you take a negative reaction, and the progress is calculated by the following formula: progress = your positive reaction times – your negative reaction times * punishment. When progress reaches your goal, this attention is achieved. You can modify the records in the calendar view, but in order to maintain the authenticity of records, your modification times will be shown at the upper right corner of the calendar.</string>
    <string name="tips_periodic_care">* You can edit the title by clicking it, but the title can’t be empty.\n\n* “Description” is an editable text that can be used for recording attention’s background, creating reason, persisting motivation, stories or something else you’d like to write down. By the way, this text’s title is also editable, you can edit it by clicking the last edited time text at the bottom of description.\n\n* In “progress” interface, you can check/uncheck the attention by clicking the progress bar.\n\n* In “progress” interface, by clicking the period length showing text at the upper right corner of the progress bar, its content will switch to this attention’s creating date.\n\n* In “records” interface, you can view your records by clicking the dates on the calendar. Moreover, we use color to show the status of a day, blue represents it’s this attention’s creating day, green represents there is positive record at this day, red represents there is negative record at this day, gray represents there is records at this day, but the day’s progress is 0, today is highlighted as deep blue. \n\n* You can share your attention to your friends as a long screenshot by clicking the share button on the title bar, the screenshot will be saved at SD-card/My Optimize/Screenshots.\n\n* Periodic Attention:\n\n\t\tYou can record your habit forming process on it, and the habit need to be periodic. For example: “Keep early hours”, “Exercise three times a week”. When creating a periodic attention, besides the goal and punishment, you also need to set its periodic time (the minimum is 1 day). You can record and cancel the record repeatedly in a single cycle, but when the cycle is passed, you can’t modify the existing record. When the new cycle starts, the state of attention will refresh automatically.\n\n\t\tMoreover, you can attach two additional attribute with it: sub-item number and record time limitation. When you set sub-item number, then in a single cycle you can record as many times as the number you set, for example: “Exercise three times a week”, since in a single cycle you need to record 3 times, you should set its sub-item number to 3. When you set record time limitation, than only in the time you set can you do recording. The two attribute can also be combined together, for example: “Keep early hours”, you can set its sub-item number to 2 and record time limitation to “6:30-7:30, 21:30-22:30”.</string>
    <string name="tips_new_problem">* Rank shows the seriousness and importance of the problem, you can change the rank according to problem’s solving progress.\n\n*Problem：\n\n\t\tIn our daily life, we usually feel unhappy, sad, or fidgety. Whatever it is, if we don’t feel happy, there must be something wrong in our life, which means we need to find the problem and try to solve it, or things would only become even worse. When you find the problem, no matter what the problem is, it can be solved through 3 steps: 1. Describe the problem: make clear about its background, result and seriousness, then define it in your own language; 2. Analyze the problem: find out what caused the problem, you may use the information in step 1 to help you work it out; 3. Solve the problem: give out you solution according to problem’s cause. Based on this simple but useful theory, you can help yourself solve your problems by creating “problem” in this app. A “problem” include 3 texts that can record your description, analyzation and solution of the problem. Maybe this theory seems too simple and useless, but if you practice it with rational thinking, you will find out that it’s invincible. In addition, you can think about how to solve the problem at any time, and write down you thinking result when you are convenient to open your phone. Moreover, generally don’t expect to solve the problem within only several days, because solving a problem is not such easy. Therefore, don’t give up solving a problem simply because you can’t solve it quickly, it’s ok to just write down the problem and solve it when you have time.</string>
    <string name="tips_problem">* You can edit the title by clicking it, but the title can’t be empty.\n\n* The color of the vertical line to the left of the title shows the problem’s rank.\n\n* You can change problem’s rank according to its solving progress at any time.\n\n* If you think the problem is already solved, you can click its status button to set its status to be “solved”.\n\n* You can share your problem to your friends as a long screenshot by clicking the share button on the title bar, the screenshot will be saved at SD-card/My Optimize/Screenshots.\n\n*Problem：\n\n\t\tIn our daily life, we usually feel unhappy, sad, or fidgety. Whatever it is, if we don’t feel happy, there must be something wrong in our life, which means we need to find the problem and try to solve it, or things would only become even worse. When you find the problem, no matter what the problem is, it can be solved through 3 steps: 1. Describe the problem: make clear about its background, result and seriousness, then define it in your own language; 2. Analyze the problem: find out what caused the problem, you may use the information in step 1 to help you work it out; 3. Solve the problem: give out you solution according to problem’s cause. Based on this simple but useful theory, you can help yourself solve your problems by creating “problem” in this app. A “problem” include 3 texts that can record your description, analyzation and solution of the problem. Maybe this theory seems too simple and useless, but if you practice it with rational thinking, you will find out that it’s invincible. In addition, you can think about how to solve the problem at any time, and write down you thinking result when you are convenient to open your phone. Moreover, generally don’t expect to solve the problem within only several days, because solving a problem is not such easy. Therefore, don’t give up solving a problem simply because you can’t solve it quickly, it’s ok to just write down the problem and solve it when you have time.</string>
    <string name="tips_help">* Here we only offer an overall introduction, for more details, please refer to tips (with a bulb icon) on the top of every interface.</string>
    <string name="tips_history">* You can only view the archived items, but not edit.\n\n* You can share your attention/problem to your friends as a long screenshot by clicking the share button on the title bar, the screenshot will be saved at SD-card/My Optimize/Screenshots.</string>
    <string name="tips_settings"><![CDATA[* In settings, we offered 3 functions: set the way of sorting the attentions/problem; backup your data; set app’s language. About the first function, if you disable the auto-sorting option, then you can sort your attentions/problems by dragging them, but if the auto-sorting option is on, this is disabled. About the second function, the data is backed up at SD-card/My Optimize/Backup. About the third function, at present we only offered Simplified Chinese and English (US). The English is translated by the developer, so there might be some translation errors, if you find translation errors or is willing to help us translate the app to more languages, please click sliding menu -> feedback or sliding menu -> about -> help with translation.]]></string>
    <string name="tips_settings_backup">* You can back up your current data by clicking the backup button on the title bar.\n\n* Click the existed backup to edit it (delete/revert).\n\n* When you revert to an existing backup, the current data will be backed up automatically.\n\n* The data is backed up at SD-card/My Optimize/Backup, the directory won’t be deleted when the app is uninstalled.</string>
    <string name="tips_settings_language"><![CDATA[* At present we only offered Simplified Chinese and English (US). The English is translated by the developer, so there might be some translation errors, if you find translation errors or is willing to help us translate the app to more languages, please click sliding menu -> feedback or sliding menu -> about -> help with translation.]]></string>
    <string name="postpone_start">Activate at tomorrow</string>
    <string name="attention_not_activated">This attention is not activated at present</string>

</resources>
 